<text>
<url>
http://www.myopinions-carl.com/2010/07/obama-failures-listed.html</url>
<total_score>
<wrapper_score>
<score>
compound:0.3182      </score>
<score>
neg:0.0      </score>
<score>
neu:0.859      </score>
<score>
pos:0.141      </score>
</wrapper_score>
<wrapper_score>
<score>
compound:-0.9183      </score>
<score>
neg:0.214      </score>
<score>
neu:0.721      </score>
<score>
pos:0.065      </score>
</wrapper_score>
<wrapper_score>
<score>
compound:-0.2144      </score>
<score>
neg:0.13      </score>
<score>
neu:0.738      </score>
<score>
pos:0.132      </score>
</wrapper_score>
<wrapper_score>
<score>
compound:0.2263      </score>
<score>
neg:0.047      </score>
<score>
neu:0.893      </score>
<score>
pos:0.059      </score>
</wrapper_score>
<wrapper_score>
<score>
compound:-0.8779      </score>
<score>
neg:0.28      </score>
<score>
neu:0.72      </score>
<score>
pos:0.0      </score>
</wrapper_score>
</total_score>
<summary>
Labels: Acorn, Barack Obama, Clinton, Gas Prices, George W Bush, GM, Google Obama, Hillary Clinton, List of Obama Failures, narcissist, Obama Failures, Oil Prices, President Obama, worst president since Carter
Please visit the new poll at the end of the post to express your views.
Websites from the Author of this articleAlso consider reading this companion article which is also a list type format and growing much faster in both "failures" but also popularity of the article:Updated 3/20/16Here are a couple positives:* President Obama used intelligence gleaned from interrogations he disagreed with to make the right decision to go after and kill Osama Bin Laden.
Please also visit my new poll (as of June 2013) to give your opinion as to "Who is the most dishonest person in the Media"It is found at the end of this article:List of Media Lies, Dishonesty, & FailuresThese two positives still do not in any way make up for this list of failures & extreme leftist views & hatred of anyone who has achieved anything in life via hard work!
He could have ignored this (as many of his past remarks/actions suggest he could have); however our President did the "right Thing";*Turning over his actual Birth CertificateWhile this controversy may not go away and while these documents may well be forged (according to some); either way this is a minor issue IMHO and detracts from serious debate of why in most cases this man is the worst president in our Nation's history.Submit your site to a web directory for free This site is listed under Government Operations Directory I have been working in the business of professional aquarium and pond maintenance and design since 1978.During this time I have carried out many research project as well, often becoming well known in my field in areas such as Aquarium/Pond UV Sterilization and Aquarium Lighting.See these two articles:This includes becoming an expert in aquarium/pond products and what determines whether a product will do the job they were designed for.
</summary>
<keywords>
['socialist', 'nations', 'failings', 'site', 'visit', 'list', 'date', 'way', 'right', 'failures', 'president', 'obama', 'prices', 'worst']
</keywords>
<date>
None
</date>
</text>
